C:\My Invoice Apps\src\App.jsx
  134:6 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useEffect has missing dependencies: 'isHandshaking' and 'isVerified'. Either include them or remove the dependency array.
  176:25 no-unused-vars - 'setIsHandshaking' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\components\BarcodeScanner.jsx
  20:18 no-unused-vars - 'error' is defined but never used.
  48:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useEffect has a missing dependency: 'startCamera'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\components\DocumentTemplate.jsx
  1:10 no-unused-vars - 'useLocalStorage' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  2:10 no-unused-vars - 'useTheme' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  3:10 no-unused-vars - 'usePlan' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  51:44 no-unused-vars - 'docType' is defined but never used.
  58:32 no-unused-vars - 'docType' is defined but never used.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\components\KasirPinLogin.jsx
  1:20 no-unused-vars - 'useEffect' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  3:10 no-unused-vars - 'supabase' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  8:13 no-unused-vars - 'user' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\components\Layout.jsx
  97:45 no-unused-vars - 'Icon' is defined but never used.
  174:13 no-unused-vars - 't' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\components\LimitModal.jsx
  13:16 no-unused-vars - 'lang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  18:11 no-unused-vars - 'bgSolid' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\components\Navbar.jsx
  12:13 no-unused-vars - 'isPro' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\components\NotificationBell.jsx
  55:13 no-unused-vars - 'lang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  56:13 no-unused-vars - 'effectivePlan' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  56:28 no-unused-vars - 'profile' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  64:12 no-unused-vars - 'invoiceCount' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  64:26 no-unused-vars - 'setInvoiceCount' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  65:12 no-unused-vars - 'clientCount' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  65:25 no-unused-vars - 'setClientCount' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  174:11 no-unused-vars - 'divider' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\components\OnboardingModal.jsx
  24:13 no-unused-vars - 'lang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\components\PrivateRoute.jsx
  5:10 no-unused-vars - 'useEffect' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  9:11 no-unused-vars - 'showToast' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  10:11 no-unused-vars - 'lang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  11:9 no-unused-vars - 'hasShownToast' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\components\Sidebar.jsx
  1:31 no-unused-vars - 'useMemo' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  12:10 no-unused-vars - 'useLocalStorage' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  34:16 no-unused-vars - 'lang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  36:9 no-unused-vars - 'isPro' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  36:16 no-unused-vars - 'isPremium' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  36:27 no-unused-vars - 'checkDownloadLimit' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  36:47 no-unused-vars - 'incrementDownload' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  38:35 no-unused-vars - 'getKasirDailyCount' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  38:88 no-unused-vars - 'refreshUsage' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  43:24 no-unused-vars - 'logout' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  45:26 no-unused-vars - 'canAccessAdvancedKasir' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  63:12 no-unused-vars - 'debtAlertCount' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  254:44 no-unused-vars - 'Icon' is defined but never used.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\components\SignaturePad.jsx
  19:13 no-unused-vars - 'lang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  91:11 no-unused-vars - 'useSaved' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\components\StatCard.jsx
  2:10 no-unused-vars - 'useCountUp' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  9:13 no-unused-vars - 'lang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\components\UpgradeModal.jsx
  11:13 no-unused-vars - 'lang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  12:74 no-unused-vars - 'isAdmin' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\components\UpgradePrompt.jsx
  7:13 no-unused-vars - 'lang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\components\kasir\Cart.jsx
  10:13 no-unused-vars - 'user' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  63:17 no-unused-vars - 'val' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\components\kasir\OutletSwitcher.jsx
  8:13 no-unused-vars - 'lang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\components\kasir\PaymentModal.jsx
  89:27 no-unused-vars - 'error' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\components\kasir\ProductModal.jsx
  36:12 no-unused-vars - 'isLoadingIngredients' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  75:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useEffect has a missing dependency: 'loadIngredients'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
  250:11 no-unused-vars - 'isSellableView' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\components\kasir\ReceiptModal.jsx
  12:16 no-unused-vars - 'lang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\components\kasir\ThermalReceipt.jsx
  6:13 no-unused-vars - 'isPremium' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  7:16 no-unused-vars - 'lang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\context\AuthContext.jsx
  31:21 no-unused-vars - 'error' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  48:14 no-unused-vars - 'e' is defined but never used.
  59:21 no-unused-vars - 'error' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  84:20 no-unused-vars - '_' is defined but never used.
  97:14 no-unused-vars - 'e' is defined but never used.
  178:6 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useEffect has a missing dependency: 'profile'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
  261:14 no-unused-vars - 'e' is defined but never used.
  266:9 no-unused-vars - 'canStartTrial' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  278:9 no-unused-vars - 'proExpired' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\context\PlanContext.jsx
  50:43 no-unused-vars - 'trialActive' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  87:18 no-unused-vars - '_' is defined but never used.
  225:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useCallback has a missing dependency: 'isUltimate'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
  232:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useCallback has a missing dependency: 'isUltimate'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
  240:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useCallback has a missing dependency: 'isUltimate'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
  250:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useCallback has a missing dependency: 'isUltimate'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
  260:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useCallback has a missing dependency: 'isUltimate'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
  270:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useCallback has a missing dependency: 'isUltimate'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
  280:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useCallback has a missing dependency: 'isUltimate'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
  290:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useCallback has a missing dependency: 'isUltimate'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
  299:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useCallback has a missing dependency: 'isUltimate'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
  324:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useCallback has a missing dependency: 'isUltimate'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
  338:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useCallback has a missing dependency: 'isUltimate'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\context\ThemeContext.jsx
  1:48 no-unused-vars - 'useState' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\hooks\useLocalStorage.js
  47:13 no-unused-vars - 'start' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\About.jsx
  1:10 no-unused-vars - 'useState' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  49:13 no-unused-vars - 'user' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\Affiliate.jsx
  8:13 no-unused-vars - 'lang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  9:11 no-unused-vars - 'navigate' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\AuditLog.jsx
  9:10 no-unused-vars - 'formatIDR' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  13:16 no-unused-vars - 'lang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  169:49 no-unused-vars - 'index' is defined but never used.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\Blog.jsx
  67:11 no-unused-vars - 'navigate' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  68:13 no-unused-vars - 'user' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\CatatanBisnis.jsx
  3:10 no-unused-vars - 'useLocalStorage' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  8:21 no-unused-vars - 'formatCompactCurrency' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  9:34 no-unused-vars - 'isToday' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  16:10 no-unused-vars - 'recordAudit' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  30:16 no-unused-vars - 'lang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  34:19 no-unused-vars - 'effectivePlan' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  34:34 no-unused-vars - 'isAdmin' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  108:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useEffect has a missing dependency: 'fetchEntries'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
  273:38 no-unused-vars - 'reason' is defined but never used.
  279:21 no-unused-vars - 'error' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\Dashboard.jsx
  5:10 no-unused-vars - 'useLocalStorage' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  7:40 no-unused-vars - 'isThisMonth' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  20:39 no-unused-vars - 'isAdmin' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  21:9 no-unused-vars - 'canAccessReport' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  21:26 no-unused-vars - 'canAccessAdvancedKasir' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  22:9 no-unused-vars - 'canAccessMultiOutlet' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  22:31 no-unused-vars - 'canAccessKaryawan' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  23:9 no-unused-vars - 'canWhiteLabelStruk' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  23:29 no-unused-vars - 'canAccessHPP' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  28:32 no-unused-vars - 'getQuotationCount' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  28:51 no-unused-vars - 'getPOCount' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  28:63 no-unused-vars - 'getTandaTerimaCount' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  29:36 no-unused-vars - 'isPro' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  32:11 no-unused-vars - 'isFree' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  78:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useEffect has missing dependencies: 'fetchDashboardData' and 'user'. Either include them or remove the dependency array.
  322:11 no-unused-vars - 'nowTime' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  333:11 no-unused-vars - 'totalHutang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  337:11 no-unused-vars - 'unpaidDisplay' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\ForgotPassword.jsx
  8:11 no-unused-vars - 'lang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\HelpCenter.jsx
  255:60 no-unused-vars - 'key' is defined but never used.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\HitungHPP.jsx
  135:37 no-unused-vars - 'Icon' is defined but never used.
  180:11 no-unused-vars - 'bg' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  595:54 no-unused-vars - 'i' is defined but never used.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\HutangPiutang.jsx
  3:10 no-unused-vars - 'useLocalStorage' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  31:16 no-unused-vars - 'isPremium' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  31:27 no-unused-vars - 'checkDownloadLimit' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  31:47 no-unused-vars - 'incrementDownload' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  32:58 no-unused-vars - 'getHutangPiutangCount' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  36:13 no-unused-vars - 'effectivePlan' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  37:13 no-unused-vars - 'lang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  95:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useEffect has a missing dependency: 'fetchData'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
  144:33 no-unused-vars - 'formData' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\Invoice.jsx
  1:20 no-unused-vars - 'useRef' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  8:44 no-unused-vars - 'formatInputNumber' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  16:10 no-unused-vars - 'isNative' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  52:65 no-unused-vars - 'refreshUsage' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  52:79 no-unused-vars - 'getInvoiceCount' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  53:9 no-unused-vars - 'currentLimits' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  68:12 no-unused-vars - 'kwitansiData' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  69:12 no-unused-vars - 'cashbook' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  114:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useEffect has missing dependencies: 'fetchClients', 'fetchInvoices', and 'user'. Either include them or remove the dependency array.
  410:11 no-unused-vars - 'handleDeleteHistory' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  461:15 no-unused-vars - 'oldStatus' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  463:15 no-unused-vars - 'amount' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  539:11 no-unused-vars - 'symCur' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  620:47 no-unused-vars - 'st' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\Karir.jsx
  1:10 no-unused-vars - 'useState' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  8:13 no-unused-vars - 'lang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  9:11 no-unused-vars - 'navigate' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  12:11 no-unused-vars - 'cardStyle' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\KasirMembers.jsx
  13:13 no-unused-vars - 'isPro' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  13:32 no-unused-vars - 'effectivePlan' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  45:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useEffect has a missing dependency: 'fetchMembers'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\Klien.jsx
  25:20 no-unused-vars - 'isPremium' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  25:31 no-unused-vars - 'checkClientLimit' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  33:12 no-unused-vars - 'ttrList' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  43:12 no-unused-vars - 'searchTerm' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  43:24 no-unused-vars - 'setSearchTerm' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  93:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useEffect has a missing dependency: 'fetchData'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\Kwitansi.jsx
  11:63 no-unused-vars - 'parseCurrency' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  13:25 no-unused-vars - 'incrementDocNumber' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  19:10 no-unused-vars - 'isNative' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  101:12 no-unused-vars - 'cashbook' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  101:22 no-unused-vars - 'setCashbook' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  109:12 no-unused-vars - 'statusMenuOpen' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  109:28 no-unused-vars - 'setStatusMenuOpen' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  142:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useEffect has a missing dependency: 'fetchKwitansi'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\Landing.jsx
  59:13 no-unused-vars - 'user' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  93:17 no-unused-vars - 'outcome' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\Laporan.jsx
  5:10 no-unused-vars - 'useLocalStorage' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  7:21 no-unused-vars - 'formatCompactCurrency' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  8:10 no-unused-vars - 'isThisMonth' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  35:12 no-unused-vars - 'cashbook' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  35:22 no-unused-vars - 'setCashbook' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  36:22 no-unused-vars - 'setInvoices' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  44:12 no-unused-vars - 'debts' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  267:11 no-unused-vars - 'invUnpaid' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  268:11 no-unused-vars - 'invPaid' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  269:11 no-unused-vars - 'invWaiting' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  284:11 no-unused-vars - 'openInvoicePanel' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  333:11 no-unused-vars - 'card_style' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  344:11 no-unused-vars - 'getFontSize' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\LaporanKasir.jsx
  17:16 no-unused-vars - 'lang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  18:43 no-unused-vars - 'canAccessAdvancedKasir' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  209:11 no-unused-vars - 'peakHours' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\Login.jsx
  5:10 no-unused-vars - 'supabase' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  11:40 no-unused-vars - 'session' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  35:6 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useEffect has a missing dependency: 't'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
  67:13 no-unused-vars - 'data' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\PenawaranHarga.jsx
  16:21 no-unused-vars - 'formatCompactCurrency' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  16:44 no-unused-vars - 'parseCurrency' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  18:25 no-unused-vars - 'incrementDocNumber' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  22:10 no-unused-vars - 'isNative' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  95:9 no-unused-vars - 'checkSPHLimit' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  109:18 no-unused-vars - 'setSigPos' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  138:46 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useEffect has a missing dependency: 'fetchSPH'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\Privacy.jsx
  77:11 no-unused-vars - 'navigate' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  78:13 no-unused-vars - 'user' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  81:30 no-unused-vars - 'Icon' is defined but never used.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\Profile.jsx
  16:14 no-unused-vars - 'lang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  181:14 no-unused-vars - 'e' is defined but never used.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\PurchaseOrder.jsx
  8:63 no-unused-vars - 'parseCurrency' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  71:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useEffect has a missing dependency: 'fetchData'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\Register.jsx
  5:10 no-unused-vars - 'supabase' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  10:19 no-unused-vars - 'user' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  10:34 no-unused-vars - 'authLoading' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  13:11 no-unused-vars - 'lang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\ResetPassword.jsx
  10:11 no-unused-vars - 'lang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  10:17 no-unused-vars - 'toggleLang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  58:6 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useEffect has a missing dependency: 't'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\Settings.jsx
  6:10 no-unused-vars - 'useLocalStorage' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  21:37 no-unused-vars - 'Icon' is defined but never used.
  35:16 no-unused-vars - 'lang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  37:36 no-unused-vars - 'preview' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  186:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useEffect has a missing dependency: 'fetchVouchers'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
  195:21 no-unused-vars - 'data' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\TandaTerima.jsx
  9:10 no-unused-vars - 'formatIDR' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  9:21 no-unused-vars - 'formatCompactCurrency' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  57:11 no-unused-vars - 'navigate' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  84:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useEffect has a missing dependency: 'fetchData'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\Terms.jsx
  83:11 no-unused-vars - 'navigate' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  84:13 no-unused-vars - 'user' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  87:30 no-unused-vars - 'Icon' is defined but never used.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\Upgrade.jsx
  12:16 no-unused-vars - 'lang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  15:44 no-unused-vars - 'trialActive' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  15:57 no-unused-vars - 'canStartTrial' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  15:72 no-unused-vars - 'trialDaysLeft' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  15:111 no-unused-vars - 'isAdmin' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  16:11 no-unused-vars - 'isFree' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\admin\AdminDashboard.jsx
  9:11 no-unused-vars - 't' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\kasir\Karyawan.jsx
  12:19 no-unused-vars - 'canAccessKaryawan' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  15:16 no-unused-vars - 'lang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  47:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useEffect has a missing dependency: 'loadData'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
  211:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useEffect has missing dependencies: 'loadData' and 'user'. Either include them or remove the dependency array.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\kasir\Laporan.jsx
  40:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useEffect has a missing dependency: 'loadData'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
  107:15 no-unused-vars - 'currentLocale' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  167:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useMemo has an unnecessary dependency: 'selectedDate'. Either exclude it or remove the dependency array.
  422:56 no-unused-vars - 'idx' is defined but never used.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\kasir\OutletManagement.jsx
  11:16 no-unused-vars - 'lang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\kasir\Pengeluaran.jsx
  16:16 no-unused-vars - 'lang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  73:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useEffect has a missing dependency: 'loadData'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
  92:27 no-unused-vars - 'expRes' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\pages\kasir\Stok.jsx
  9:10 no-unused-vars - 'formatIDR' is defined but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  15:16 no-unused-vars - 'lang' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
  66:8 react-hooks/exhaustive-deps - React Hook useEffect has a missing dependency: 'loadData'. Either include it or remove the dependency array.
  94:28 no-unused-vars - 'histErr' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
C:\My Invoice Apps\src\utils\whatsapp.js
  15:11 no-unused-vars - 'companyPhone' is assigned a value but never used. Allowed unused vars must match /^[A-Z_]/u.
